Night Tile
Well, the time for fun has flown by and it's already time for the ending!
Now, please let me introduce an announcement from Ms. Akane Sora.
Yes, Ukka's one-man live concert will be held on September 30 at Pivi Beach Shoebia. The title is Crescendo.
And on Saturday, October 14, we will have a one-man live at Tokyo Kinema Club.
It will be a one-man show called Deja Vu.
Both of them are different venues,
different concept, so we are looking forward to seeing you there.
Please come and join us.
What do you think is the highlight of your one-man live?
What is the highlight of your usual one-man live?
I think it is the fact that we perform without any set,
I think that is the best part of Ukka, to deliver our songs, dances, and performances to the audience,
Please feel the performance of Ukka with all your heart and soul.
Next, here is the other one.
Yes, it will be held on Sunday, October 29 at Yokohama Arena.
Stapla Idol Festival Autumn New Song Recording Festival will be held on Sunday, October 29th at Yokohama Arena.
Yuka will perform!
Yay!
I have been unable to attend the Stapla festival in January because of my health condition.
I was sick and realized that I was sick, which means that I was absent from the Stapla festival for the first time in a long time because I was sick,
It's been a long time since I've been to a staple festival,
I am looking forward to it. Please come, everyone.
Please come.
This time, all the groups will perform their first song,
or the final song of a new song,
The bar is set a little high for each group,
I think this will be a fan event that you, Mil Sateria, are looking forward to,
This is a place where you will have a chance to meet various senior members of STAPLA.
What do you think? Akane-san.
Are there any members in other groups that you are close with?
Who are your good friends in other groups?
Airi Fujita from Crown Top,
Rion Kitami from Talk,
I also get along well with everyone in Ibitsuyu,
I would like to have a chance to talk with other groups that I have never been involved with before.I would like to be able to talk with groups I have not been involved with very much.
Do you want to take a picture with this person, or do you have a commitment to do your best to take a picture of this person?
Do you want to take pictures?
Well, let's see,
I'd like to meet with Kazamino Noka of EBITSUYU GAKU.
Yes, I understand.
Are you good-looking here?
I'll do my best.
I'm sure everyone is looking forward to seeing the pictures if you can get them on Instagram or something and have a conversation with them,
I'm sure everyone is looking forward to it, so please do your best.
I hope you also enjoy the skirt-rise soup.
Yes, I will.
Lastly, Yahana-kun, I would like to present you with a tea that will cheer you up.
This time it is a blend of herbal teas for sore throats.
Yay!
This is my first time to drink herbal tea. Actually.
First time?
Yes, it is.
I don't drink tea very often.
So this is my first time drinking herbal tea,
I'll have some.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid. I'll have some of that.
I'll have some.
It tastes like it's good for your throat.
One more time.
It's delicious. Thank you very much. I'm glad.
Thank you very much for taking the time to come with us today in this heavy rain.
I'm sure the rain has stopped.
Yes, I believe it has.
Now then, please give us a cute closing remark.
Yes, thank you all for watching.
I am sure that even those of you who don't know much about Akane Sora have gotten to know a little bit more about her.
Please come and talk with me on TikTok, my blog, Instagram, and at my live performances.
Thank you very much!
This show was sponsored by Hacchi, Tokiyuki, I was sponsored by Eldis, Shigu, and Izakaya Rider #1.This program was provided by Hacchi, Tokiyuki, I am Eldis, Shigu, and Izakaya Rider #1.
Thank you all for your many offerings.
Please come again when I am on. See you~.